{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "物理",
      "answer": "Wùlǐ | physics"
    },
    {
      "question": "化学",
      "answer": "Huàxué | chemistry"
    },
    {
      "question": "数学",
      "answer": "Shùxué | mathematics"
    },
    {
      "question": "音乐",
      "answer": "Yīnyuè | music"
    },
    {
      "question": "历史",
      "answer": "Lìshǐ | history"
    },
    {
      "question": "哲学",
      "answer": "Zhéxué | philosophy"
    },
    {
      "question": "经济",
      "answer": "Jīngjì | economics"
    },
    {
      "question": "教育",
      "answer": "Jiàoyù | education"
    },
    {
      "question": "选修",
      "answer": "Xuǎnxiū | to take an elective course"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化",
      "answer": "Wénhuà | culture"
    }
  ]
}
